Register of the Robert Daniel Murphy papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Later Years I, 1959-1978 (Boxes 93-143)
  - Correspondence
    - McMahon, William, 1970 (Folder 10)
    - McNamara, Robert S., 1975 (Folder 11)
    - Meany, George, 1969-1975 (Folder 12)
    - Mefret, Noel, 1969-1971 (Folder 13)
    - Melandri, Pierre, 1974 (Folder 14)
    - Melbourne, Roy M., 1971 (Folder 15)
    - Menuhin, Moshe, 1971 (Folder 16)
    - Menuhin, Yehudi, 1968-1976 (Folder 17)
    - Menzies, Robert G., 1972 (Folder 18)
    - Merchant, Livingston, 1960-1967 (Folder 19)
    - Meyer, Armin, 1969-1971 (Folder 20)
    - Meyer, Charles A., 1972-1973 (Folder 21)
    - Meyer, Frank, 1969 (Folder 22)
    - Meyer, John M., Jr., 1970-1976 (Folder 23)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II, 1969-1975 (Folder 24)
    - Milburn, Bryan, 1967 (Folder 25)
    - Miller, Gething C., 1971 (Folder 26)
    - Millington-Drake, Eugen, 1972 (Folder 27)
    - Moellering, John H., 1974 (Folder 28)
    - Mommsen, Ernst Wolf, 1972 (Folder 29)
    - Monnet, Jean, 1975-1977 (Folder 30)
    - Moore, John D.J., 1969 (Folder 31)
    - Moore, Walden, 1970-1971 (Folder 32)
    - Moorer, Thomas H., 1971-1975 (Folder 33)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1969-1975 (Folder 34)
    - Moro, Aldo, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Mountbatten, The Earl of, 1970 (Folder 2)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1976 (Folder 3)
    - Mulligan, Dennis J., 1969-1974 (Folder 4)
    - Mundt, Karl E., 1968 (Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Charles J.V., 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Murphy, Gavin, 1977 (Folder 7)
    - Murphy, Richard W., 1974 (Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Robert D., Jr., 1970 (Folder 9)
    - Murphy, Thomas A., 1975 (Folder 10)
    - Nagorski, Zygmunt, 1975 (Folder 11)
    - Nakashima, Nobuyuki, 1975-1977 (Folder 12)
    - Nakasone, Yasuhiro, 1973 (Folder 13)
    - Nara, Yasuhiko, 1967-1969 (Folder 14)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1967-1975 (Folder 15)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1972-1976 (Folder 16)
    - National Foreign Trade Council, 1969 (Folder 17)
    - National Planning Association, 1970 (Folder 18)
    - Neff, John C., 1967 (Folder 19)
    - Nehru, B.K., 1967 (Folder 20)
    - Nelson, Walter Henry, 1970 (Folder 21)
    - Newsom, David D., 1972 (Folder 22)
    - Newton, Henry, 1969 (Folder 23)
    - Nitze, Paul H., 1974 (Folder 24)
    - Nixon, Patricia, 1969-1971 (Folder 25)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1967-1976 (Folder 26)
    - Norden, Carl F., 1967 (Folder 27)
    - Norris, Robert B., 1971 (Folder 28)
    - Norstad, Lauris, 1971 (Folder 29)
    - O'Brien, John A., 1973 (Folder 30)
    - O'Brien, William, 1970-1976 (Folder 31)
    - O'Connor, Roderic, 1972 (Folder 32)
    - Oehlert, B.H., Jr., 1970 (Folder 33)
    - Oestreicher, Sylvan, 1970-1972 (Folder 34)
    - Offie, Carmel, 1967-1971 (Folder 35)
    - Onassis, Aristotle, 1973 (Folder 36)
    - Oppenheimer, Franz M., 1967-1968 (Folder 37)
    - Osborn, David, 1973 (Folder 38)
    - Overby, Andrew N., 1967-1971 (Folder 39)
    - Ovidio, Antonio d', 1969 (Folder 40)
    - Packard, David, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Packer, Earl L., 1975 (Folder 2)
    - Paley, William S., 1975 (Folder 3)
    - Paris American Club, 1968 (Folder 4)
    - Parks, Robert B., 1967 (Folder 5)
    - Parsons, Jeanne, 1973 (Folder 6)
    - Pasquet, Mme. Maurice, 1975 (Folder 7)
    - Pasquier, Pierre du, 1967-1969 (Folder 8)
    - Pasquier, Verena du, 1976 (Folder 9)
    - Pauphilet, B., 1968-1969 (Folder 10)
    - Peale, Norman Vincent, 1975 (Folder 11)
    - Pearson, Lester, 1967 (Folder 12)
    - Pedersen, Richard F., 1971-1975 (Folder 13)
    - Perkins, Richard, 1975 (Folder 14)
    - Peterfi, William O., 1972 (Folder 15)
    - Petersen, Howard C., 1975 (Folder 16)
    - Petree, Virginia H., 1974-1975 (Folder 17)
    - Petrov, Vladimir, 1969 (Folder 18)
    - Philpott, Robert J., 1976 (Folder 19)
    - Phleger, Herman, 1972-1975 (Folder 20)
    - Picot, Willy George, 1972 (Folder 21)
    - Pinay, Antoine, 1973 (Folder 22)
    - Pinkley, Virgil, 1970-1972 (Folder 23)
    - Plaza, Galo, 1970 (Folder 24)
    - Plimpton, Francis T.P., 1971-1975 (Folder 25)
    - Plitt, James R., 1970-1976 (Folder 26)
    - Polk, Mrs. Judd N., 1975 (Folder 27)
    - Popper, David H., 1969 (Folder 28)
    - Porter, Dwight J., 1970 (Folder 29)
    - Porter, William J., 1971-1974 (Folder 30)
    - Potter, Gary, 1967 (Folder 31)
    - Prochnow, Herbert V., 1971 (Folder 32)
    - Protter, Benjamin, 1968-1975 (Folder 33)
    - Rabb, Maxwell M., 1967 (Folder 34)
    - Rabin, Yitzhak, 1970 (Folder 35)
    - Radford, Arthur W., 1970 (Folder 36)
    - Radvanyi, Janos, 1970 (Folder 37)
    - Raghavan, Jai D., 1975 (Folder 38)
    - Ramsbotham, Peter, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Ramsey, James, 1971 (Folder 2)
    - Read, Benjamin H., 1969 (Folder 3)
    - Rees, David, 1969 (Folder 4)
    - Reid, W. Stafford, 1970 (Folder 5)
    - Reischauer, Edwin O. and Haru, 1961-1977 (Folder 6)
    - Republican National Committee, 1967 (Folder 7)
    - Reston, James, 1970 (Folder 8)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1975-1976 (Folder 9)
    - Rice, Louis J., Jr., 1975 (Folder 10)
    - Richardson, Elliot L., 1969-1975 (Folder 11)
    - Riddleberger, James W., 1962-1969 (Folder 12)
    - Ridgway, Matthew B., 1971-1976 (Folder 13)
    - Riess, Curt, 1976 (Folder 14)
    - Roach, Perry, 1975-1977 (Folder 15)
    - Roche, James M., 1970-1976 (Folder 16)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1970-1977 (Folder 17)
    - Rockefeller, James S., 1967 (Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller, John D., III, 1967-1975 (Folder 19)
    - Rockefeller, Mr. and Mrs. Nelson A., 1974-1977 (Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1967-1973 (Folder 21)
    - Rockwell, Stuart W., 1970-1973 (Folder 22)
    - Rogers, William P., 1970-1972 (Folder 23)
    - Rolling Stone, 1976 (Folder 24)
    - Romney, George, 1967 (Folder 25)
    - Romney Associates, 1967 (Folder 26)
    - Romulo, Carlos, 1972-1974 (Folder 27)
    - Rooney, Catherine, 1975 (Folder 28)
    - Rooney, John J., 1970-1974 (Folder 29)
    - Rosenberg, Elliot, 1973 (Folder 30)
    - Rositzke, Harry, 1975 (Folder 31)
    - Rostow, Eugene V., 1970-1976 (Folder 32)
    - Rostow, Walt W., 1969-1970 (Folder 33)
    - Roudakoff, Paul, 1976 (Folder 34)
    - Rountree, William M., 1972-1973 (Folder 35)
    - Rowan, Leslie, 1967 (Folder 36)
    - Rowney, E., 1977 (Folder 37)
    - Rubloff, Arthur, 1971-1977 (Folder 38)
    - Rubottom, R. Richard, Jr., 1967-1969 (Folder 39)
    - Rueff, Jacques, 1975 (Folder 40)
    - Rueger, William F., 1977 (Folder 41)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald H., 1975 (Folder 42)
    - Rush, Kenneth, 1974-1977 (Folder 43)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1960-1975 (Folder 44)
    - Russell, Mrs. Irving, 1974-1975 (Folder 45)
    - Rutledge, Campbell, Jr., 1967-1977 (Folder 46)
    - Saccio, Leonard J., 1970 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Safire, William, 1977 (Folder 2)
    - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1966 (Folder 3)
    - Saltzman, Charles E., 1973-1977 (Folder 4)
    - Samuels, Nathaniel, 1972-1974 (Folder 5)
    - Sandusky, Michael C., 1976 (Folder 6)
    - Sarnoff, Robert W., 1967-1975 (Folder 7)
    - Sato, Eisaku, 1967-1969 (Folder 8)
    - Satterthwaite, Joseph C., 1975 (Folder 9)
    - Sause, Mrs. Oliver, 1975 (Folder 10)
    - Scali, John A., 1973 (Folder 11)
    - Schaefer, Steve, 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Scheuer, Sidney H., 1970 (Folder 13)
    - Schlesinger, James R., 1971-1975 (Folder 14)
    - Schmidt, Helmut, 1971-1974 (Folder 15)
    - Scott, Hugh, 1967-1975 (Folder 16)
    - Scott, John, 1970-1976 (Folder 17)
    - Scranton, William M., 1976 (Folder 18)
    - Scribner, Fred C., Jr., 1961 (Folder 19)
    - Seaborg, Glenn T., 1971 (Folder 20)
    - Searle, William A., 1970-1973 (Folder 21)
    - Seeds, Robert, 1974 (Folder 22)
    - Seignious, George M., II, 1974 (Folder 23)
    - Senoussi, Badreddine, 1973 (Folder 24)
    - Shah, Konsin C., 1975-1977 (Folder 25)
    - Shaine, H.B., 1973 (Folder 26)
    - Sheean, Mrs. Vincent, 1975 (Folder 27)
    - Sheehan, John E., 1972 (Folder 28)
    - Shepley, James R., 1975 (Folder 29)
    - Shoji, Keijiro, 1971 (Folder 30)
    - Shriver, R. Sargent, Jr., 1968 (Folder 31)
    - Shultz, George, 1972-1974 (Folder 32)
    - Simon, Eugene, 1975-1977 (Folder 33)
    - Simon, William E., 1974 (Folder 34)
    - Singer, Herbert, 1967 (Folder 35)
    - Sisco, Joseph J., 1971-1974 (Folder 36)
    - Smalley, Walter, 1967 (Folder 37)
    - Smith, Carleton, 1969 (Folder 38)
    - Smith, Gerard C., 1971-1974 (Folder 39)
    - Smith, James S., 1975 (Folder 40)
    - Smith, Richard J., 1976 (Folder 41)
    - Smith, Richard W., 1976 (Folder 42)
    - Sneider, Richard L., 1972 (Folder 43)
    - Societe Anonyme Belge D'Exploitation de la Navigation Aerienne (SABENA), 1969 (Folder 44)
    - Soffer, Elie, 1967-1973 (Folder 45)
    - Soustelle, Jacques, 1975 (Folder 46)
    - Spellman, Francis Cardinal, 1964 (Folder 47)
    - Spivak, Lawrence, 1975 (Folder 48)
    - Springer, Axel, 1971-1972 (Folder 49)
    - Stabler, Wells, 1974 (Folder 50)
    - Staercke, Andre de, 1969 (Folder 51)
    - Standish, Myles, 1975 (Folder 52)
    - Stans, Maurice, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Stanton, Frank, 1972-1975 (Folder 2)
    - Steedman, Alec, 1960-1976 (Folder 3)
    - Steeves, John M., 1967-1970 (Folder 4)
    - Stegmaier, John L., 1971 (Folder 5)
    - Stephens, John W., 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Stevens, Robert, 1971-1977 (Folder 7)
    - Stoessel, Walter, 1968 (Folder 8)
    - Stone, Galen L., 1975 (Folder 9)
    - Straus, Oscar S., II, 1969-1972 (Folder 10)
    - Straus, Ralph I., 1972-1976 (Folder 11)
    - Strauss, Lewis L., 1969-1971 (Folder 12)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1967-1972 (Folder 13)
    - Struelens, Michel, 1976 (Folder 14)
    - Sugahara, K., 1970-1971 (Folder 15)
    - Sullivan, Joseph T.P., 1972-1977 (Folder 16)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs, 1974 (Folder 17)
    - Sun Yun-suan, 1974-1977 (Folder 18)
    - Surrey Probation Area, 1961 (Folder 19)
    - Symington, W. Stuart, 1969-1975 (Folder 20)
    - Taft, Philip, 1972 (Folder 21)
    - Tanguy, Charles R., 1969-1972 (Folder 22)
    - Tasca, Henry, 1971-1975 (Folder 23)
    - Teissier, Jacques, 1973-1977 (Folder 24)
    - Tello, Manuel, 1964 (Folder 25)
    - Thai, Nguyen, 1969 (Folder 26)
    - Thompson, Mr. and Mrs. Llewellyn, 1967-1977 (Folder 27)
    - Togo, Fumihiko, 1977 (Folder 28)
    - Tomabechi, T., 1975 (Folder 29)
    - Torres, Baron de las, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Tournaire, J.A., 1975 (Folder 2)
    - Trebesch, Herbert, 1969 (Folder 3)
    - Tresize, Philip, 1969 (Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission, 1975 (Folder 5)
    - Trowbridge, A.B., 1967 (Folder 6)
    - Turner, Stansfield, 1977 (Folder 7)
    - Turner, William C., 1976 (Folder 8)
    - Tute, Warren, 1976 (Folder 9)
    - Tuthill, John W., 1970-1974 (Folder 10)
    - Twining, Nathan, 1960 (Folder 11)
    - Twitchell, Kenaston, 1967-1975 (Folder 12)
    - Ungerer, Werner, 1976 (Folder 13)
    - United Nations Association of the United States of America, 1969-1970 (Folder 14)
    - United States Council, 1975 (Folder 15)
    - United States Council of the International Chamber of Commerce, 1967 (Folder 16)
    - United States Korea Economic Council, 1975 (Folder 17)
    - United States Mission to the United Nations, 1975 (Folder 18)
    - University Club, 1969-1976 (Folder 19)
    - Upston, John E., 1968-1975 (Folder 20)
    - Ushiba, Nobuhiko, 1971-1973 (Folder 21)
    - Vailati, Vanna, 1966 (Folder 22)
    - Vance, Cyrus, 1976-1977 (Folder 23)
    - Vernon, Raymond, 1974-1976 (Folder 24)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1972-1975 (Folder 25)
    - Volcker, Paul A., 1975 (Folder 26)
    - Wallin, Paul J., 1973 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Walmsley, Walter N., 1960 (Folder 2)
    - Watson, Thomas J., Jr., undated (Folder 3)
    - Watts, W. Walter, 1967 (Folder 4)
    - Watts, William, 1977 (Folder 5)
    - Waugh, Samuel C., 1961 (Folder 6)
    - Webb, James E., 1968 (Folder 7)
    - Wedemeyer, A.C., 1970 (Folder 8)
    - Weinstein, Martin E., 1968 (Folder 9)
    - Weisbrod, Ray, 1961 (Folder 10)
    - Weyl, Nathaniel, 1967 (Folder 11)
    - Whitcomb, Philip W., 1969-1977 (Folder 12)
    - Whitehouse, Charles S., 1975 (Folder 13)
    - Whitman, Ann C., 1961-1975 (Folder 14)
    - Wiley, Alexander, 1960 (Folder 15)
    - Woods, Rose Mary, 1969-1972 (Folder 16)
    - Wright, Jerauld, 1969-1977 (Folder 17)
    - Wriston, Henry, 1967-1975 (Folder 18)
    - Wyden, Peter H., 1970 (Folder 19)
    - Wyman, Thomas H., 1970 (Folder 20)
    - Yamazaki, Toshio, 1974 (Folder 21)
    - Yasukawa, Takeshi, 1973-1976 (Folder 22)
    - Yeh, George, 1973 (Folder 23)
    - Yen, C.K., 1975 (Folder 24)
    - Yost, Charles W., 1970 (Folder 25)
    - Young, R.A., 1970 (Folder 26)
    - Zablocki, Clement J., 1976-1977 (Folder 27)
    - Zahedi, Ardeshir, 1973-1974 (Folder 28)
    - Zahn, Joachim, 1970-1976 (Folder 29)
    - Zakaria, H.M.A., 1974 (Folder 30)
    - Zanuck, Darryl F., 1970 (Folder 31)
    - Zayas, Alfred M. de, 1976-1977 (Folder 32)
    - Zorlu, Fatin Rusto, 1960 (Folder 33)
    - Zurhellen, J. Owen, Jr., 1975-1977 (Folder 34)
  - Office file as member of the Commission on the Organization of the Government for the Conduct of Foreign Policy
    - General
      - March-November, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 1-7)
      - November-December, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 1-6)
      - January-June, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 1-7)
      - July-December, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 1-11)
      - January-June, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 1-12)
    - Summaries of testimony, June, 1973 -September, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Printed report, Appendices, volumes 1-4 (Box 133, Folder 1-5)
    - Appendices, volumes 5-7 (Box 134, Folder 1-3)
  - Subject file. Printed material, memoranda, correspondence, and reports, 1959-1978
    - American Embassy, Bern, Switzerland (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - American Freedom from Hunger Foundation (Folder 2)
    - American Institute for Free Labor Development (Folder 3)
    - Association Internationale des Etudiants en Sciences Economiques et Commerciales (Folder 4)
    - Association de la Liberation Francaise du, 8 Novembre 1942 (Folder 5-6)
    - Atlantic Council (Folder 7)
    - Baker, William O. (Folder 8)
    - Behm, Douglas (Folder 9)
    - Bennett, W. Tapley, Jr. (Folder 10)
    - Berlin (Folder 11)
    - Bilderberg Group (Folder 12-14)
    - Bilderberg Group (Box 136, Folder 1-15)
    - Bilderberg Group (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
    - Bishop, Max W. (Folder 3)
    - Brookings Institution Seminar, November 12, 1975 (Folder 4)
    - Bullitt, William C. (Folder 5)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Folder 6)
    - Catholic Church Encyclical (Folder 7)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency (Folder 8)
    - Chiang Kai-shek (Folder 9)
    - China (Folder 10-13)
    - Citadel (Folder 14)
    - Clay, Lucius D. (Folder 15)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 138, Folder 1-2)
    - Dominican Republic (Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Folder 4)
    - Far East-America Council (Folder 5)
    - France-America Society (Folder 6)
    - Fund for Peace (Folder 7)
    - Geopolitics (Folder 8)
    - George C. Marshall Research Foundation (Folder 9)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Folder 10)
    - Greece (Folder 11)
    - Gruber, Karl (Folder 12)
    - Houghton, Amory (Folder 13)
    - Intelligence service (Folder 14)
    - International economic relations (Folder 15)
    - International Executive Service Corps (Folder 16)
    - Italy (Folder 17)
    - Japan - Economic conditions (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Japan Fund (Folder 2)
    - Japan Society (Folder 3-4)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Folder 5)
    - Jolly, Edwin J. (Folder 6)
    - Lamont, Thomas (Folder 7)
    - Marshall Plan (Folder 8)
    - Mesta, Perle (Folder 9)
    - Miscellany (Folder 10-11)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company (Folder 12)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 140, Folder 1-6)
    - National Export Expansion Council (Folder 7-8)
    - National Planning Association (Folder 9)
    - North African Economic Board (Folder 10)
    - Pakistan Cyclone Relief Fund (Box 141, Folder 1-8)
    - Project Hope (Folder 9-10)
    - Project Hope (Box 142, Folder 1-3)
    - Public Advisory Committee for Trade Negotiations (Folder 4)
    - Radio Free Europe (Folder 5-15)
    - Searle, William A. (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Tordella, Dr. (Nominee for Rockefeller Award) (Folder 2)
    - United Nations Association of the United States of America (Folder 3)
    - United States
      - Department of State (Folder 4-5)
      - Economic conditions (Folder 6)
      - Foreign relations (Folder 7)
    - United States Committee for Refugees (Folder 8)
    - United States Council of the International Chamber of Commerce (Folder 9-12)
    - United States Overseas Information and Cultural Program (Folder 13)
    - Wang Li-yen (Folder 14)
    - World Rehabilitation Fund (Folder 15)
    - World Trade Fair, Yugoslavia, September 10-12, 1970 (Folder 16)
- Oversize File I, 1943-1967
  Albums of clippings about Robert Murphy, 1949-1951; photo album; memorabilia, and various oversized materials.
  - 6 albums of clippings, 1 photograph album, Florennes, Belgium, 3 certificates commemorating appointments to the Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board, and the National Export Expansion Council, 1949-1951; 1951; 1961 and 1965, 1967 (Box 144)
  - Flag (Box 145)
  - Olive branch from tree under which Italian armistice was signed, September, 1943 (Box 146)
  - Original of cartoon (Box 146)
  - Algerian talisman, July, 1944 (Box 146)
  - Engraved desk set (Box 146)
- Phonotapes
  5 reels.
  - Notre Dame University meeting, (3 reels), April 13, 1959 (Tape 1-3)
  - Luncheon for Under Secretary of State Robert Murphy, (2 reels), circa 1959 (Tape 4-5)
- Photographs, I
  1,298 personal and official photographs.
  - 50 unidentified prints: 2 prints of Robert Murphy and others; 3 prints of Rosemary Murphy., undated (Envelope A)
  - 1 print of Mr. and Mrs. Robert Murphy (Mildred), circa 1920; 2 prints of Robert Murphy and others at the Consular Conference, Paris, 1936; 3 prints of the Murphy family, 1936. (Envelope B)
  - 2 postcards of France; 1 print of Mrs. Robert Murphy; 1 print of Robert Murphy and others; 1 unidentified print; 1 print of Edwin and Haru Reischauer and others., undated (Envelope mC)
  - 4 prints of Robert Murphy, circa 1940; 11 prints of Morocco; 13 postcards of Morocco; 3 miscellaneous prints circa 1940; 1 print of Robert Murphy and Pierre Boisson (?), 1940. (Envelope D)
  - 12 prints of Summer Welles in Paris, March, 1940; 3 prints of Sumner Welles and General Sikorski; 1 print of the RAF airplane bringing Sumner Welles to Paris; 2 prints of Welles and M. Jeanneney; 1 print of Welles and Premier Edouard Daladier; 3 prints of Welles and Sir Ronald Campbell; 3 prints of Welles and Georges Bonnet; 1 print of Welles and Paul Reynaud; 3 prints of Welles and President Albert LeBrun; 5 prints of Welles and Robert Murphy. (Envelope E)
  - 21 prints of Cherchel House and Grounds, October 21-22, 1942 (Algeria); 1 unidentified print, 1942; 3 postcards; 1 print of Robert Murphy, 1942; 1 print of Auguste Nogues, 1941; 1 print of Robert Murphy and Henri Giraud, circa 1941; 8 prints of the Murphy family, circa 1941; 5 prints of Robert Murphy and others, circa 1941; 8 unidentified prints; 1 signed print of Adolf Hitler, November 25, 1942. (Envelope m F)
  - 1 print of Dwight D. Eisenhower, Oct. 5, 1942; 1 print of General Eisenhower's staff, October 4, 1942; 1 print of soldiers dismantling an old cannon to be used in the war effort, Ft. Point, California, 1942; 1 print of Terry Allen, Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., and Louis Koeltz, June 30, 1943; 1 print of Franklin D. Roosevelt, circa 1942; 16 prints of North Africa, 1942-1943. (Envelope G)
  - 1 print of James Doolittle and others, Dec. 24, 1942; 1 print of the funeral procession of Joseph E. Welvert; 1 print of Mark Clark and others, October 4, 1942; 2 prints of George Patton, Auguste Nogues, December 19 and 20, 1942; 1 print of King George of Great Britain, Robert McClure, June 15, 1943; 1 print of J.J. McCloy and others, Cairo, 1943; 1 print of J.K. Cannon, February 6, 1943; 1 print of W.B. Smith, B.J. Gaylord, June 6, 1943; 1 print of Henri Giraud and others, November 19, 1942; 1 antiaircraft barrage over Algiers, March 26, 1943; 1 print of Bizerte, Tunisia after Allied bombing, may 13, 1943; 1 print of George Patton and others, March 15, 1943; 1 print of Laurence Wolfe and his home, 1943; 1 print of Jean F. Darlan and Mark Clark, November 22, 1942; 1 print of jean Darlan, Charles Ryder and others; 2 prints of Jean Darlan's funeral, December 26, 1942; 1 print of Jean Darlan, Andrew Cunningham, and Dwight D. Eisenhower, December 1, 1942. (Envelope H)
  - 2 prints of Dwight Eisenhower, James Doolittle, Mark Clark, Robert Murphy and others, 1942; 1 print of Francis Cardinal Spellman and others, 1943; 1 print of Dwight Eisenhower, Robert Murphy and others, 1943; 1 print of Mark Clark and others, 1942; 3 prints of American WAAC'S, North Africa, February 14, 1943; 1 print of Henri Giraud, Charles de Gaulle and others, May 29, 1943; 1 print of Georges Catroux and others, March 30, 1943; 1 print of Allied generals and officers, May 20, 1943; 2 prints of Robert Murphy and Dwight Eisenhower, Tunisia, 1943. (Envelope I)
  - Casablanca Conference, January 1943; 2 prints of Allied Military Conference - Combined Chiefs; 1 print of Franklin Roosevelt, Winston Churchill, Louis Mountbatten, Henry Arnold and others; 1 print of Elliott Roosevelt and others; 1 print of George Marshall, Henry Arnold and others;1 print of Henry Arnold and others; 1 print of Mark Clark and others; 1 print of William Leahy and others; 1 print of Franklin Roosevelt, Charles De Gaulle, Winston Churchill, and Henri Giraud; 1 print of Franklin Roosevelt and Henry Giraud; 1 print of Chiang Kai-shek, Mme. Chiang Kai-shek, Anthony Eden, Harol Macmillan, Franklin Roosevelt, Winston Churchill, Averell Harriman, Harry Hopkins and others, Nov., 1943 (Cairo Conference); 1 print of Franklin Roosevelt and Dwight Eisenhower; 1 print of Franklin Roosevelt, Winston Churchill, Harry Hopkins, Anthony Eden, President Innonu of Turkey, (Tehran Conference, November 28-December 1, 1943) (Envelope J)
  - 6 prints of Dwight Eisenhower and others, circa 1944; 1 print of Robert Murphy on his departure from Caserta, September 2, 1944; 1 print of Robert Murphy, Carmel Offie and others; 1 print of Robert Murphy and Harold Macmillan; 2 prints of Edward Stettinius, Averell Harriman and others; 2 prints of Edward Stettinius and Averell Harriman; 2 prints of Edward Stettinius, Averell Harriman, Robert Murphy; 3 prints of Edward Stettinius, Averell Harriman, Robert Murphy and others; 1 print of Edward Stettinius and Robert Murphy, May 1944; 1 print of Robert Murphy and Harold Macmillan, 1944; 1 print of Robert Murphy, Harold Macmillan and others, circa 1944. (Envelope K)
  - 1 print of Robert Murphy and others, 1944; 12 prints of Robert Murphy, 1944; 1 print of Robert Murphy, circa 1944. (Envelope L)
  - 2 prints of Robert Murphy, Carmel Offie and others, Caserta, September, 1944; 1 print of Robert Murphy and others, November, 1944; 1 print of Robert Murphy, Omar Bradley and others, November, 1944; 1 print of Edward Stettinius, Averell Harriman, Robert Murphy and others, May 1944; 2 unidentified prints. (Envelope M)
  - 1 print of W. Bedell Smith., 1944 (Envelope mN)
  - 1 print of Dwight Eisenhower, Robert Murphy, military officers, North Africa., circa 1944 (Envelope mO)
  - 8 prints of Chantier de la Jeunesse de 1'Afrique du Nord; 1 print of Harold Alexander, North Africa, 1943; 1 print of Robert Murphy; 6 prints of Robert Murphy and others; 1 print of Robert Murphy, Harold Macmillan and others; North Africa. (Envelope P)